With this exercise, we need to create a rectangle structure with the dimensions of the rectangle
and we'll need to perform some calculations on that rectangle.
We'll hop down here to the bottom, we'll make a new structure, and we'd call type rectangle.
We're going to have a length, it should be a rectangle with a G, we'll have a length,
which is an integer, and width, which is also an integer.
We're going to make some functions, we'll make a function to calculate the area.
Let's get a return in int, and to calculate the area, we multiply the length times width,
so we'll return length times width, and for parameter, it's also going to accept a rectangle,
and we'll return the rectangle width times 2 plus the length times 2.
We create this structure, it has two fields, length, and width, we have an area function,
which accepts a rectangle, so whenever we call this area function, we're going to have
an entire rectangle, which contains both the length and width, we can then access the length
and width by using the name of the variable, which is wrecked, specified here in the parameters,
a dot, and then once we have the dot, we can type in the field name, so we have either length
or width, and here in this area function, we do both, so we do wrecked dot length, multiplied
by the wrecked dot width to give us the area, and parameter is the same thing, except instead
of calculating the area, we calculate the parameter by taking each side, multiplying them by
2, and then adding them together, we're also going to make another function to print out the
information, and also take a rectangle, we use format dot print line, and we'll do another
print line, and then finally our main function will create some rectangles and then call
these functions, so we'll set the length to 3 and the width to 7, then we'll do a print info,
let'll print out the area and the parameter, and then get a modify the rectangle,
that is one of our requirements here, so we'll copy that down, so we'll double the size of the
existing rectangle, and print the results of the terminal, so we'll access the length field,
we'll use star equal to multiply the current value by 2, we'll do the same thing for the width,
so that'll double the length, and that'll double the width, we can then use a print info,
to print out the new information for the wrecked angle, once all that's done, we're going to save
and hop into terminal, run it, and see what we get, we can run this with go-run dot slash exercise
slash struct, slash structs.go, so our first rectangle has an area of 21 and a parameter of 20,
and our second rectangle after doubling the length and width, we have an area of 84 and a
parameter of 40, and that'll do it for the exercise on structures, I'll see you in the nice
presentation.